We will welcome the amazing crops of this year with some hot delicious laddoos.
Yes, Do La Kpur has had such a good harvest after so many years.
Yes.
A happy occasion like this must be celebrated.
But be careful, the children might try to steal the laddoos even before you distribute them.
Mmm!
I'll catch her attention and you take the laddoos.
The moment they look somewhere else, we will attack on those delicious laddoos.
Chutki, Masu, look over there.
There's a beautiful kite in the sky.
Oh!
But Raju, where is the kite?
Over there.
It's hidden behind the tree now.
It came out.
We didn't watch.
Leave!
Go away!
These are mine!
When children don't have anything to do, they become really mischievous.
Oh no!
Our kite doesn't have laddoos today.
Just hide!
We were just about to get those laddoos.
But Chutki and Beam came and spoiled the whole plan.
We didn't spoil the plan.
You spoiled the plan.
I am not going to spare both of you.
Oh!
Get back here, Big One!
Beam!
I am so huge that I'm unable to hide behind these teeny tiny bushes.
Oh!
Get out of your otherwise!
Yay!
Come out, say it, girl!
You're scared!
But the bushes are shivering!
No!
I am not scared!
I was just trying to look for a weapon to scare away those bulls.
Oh, Beam!
Oh, you're all young!
You're all young!
Oh, Beam!
So what do you weird experiments out there?
Oh no!
Oh!
Beam!
But who's doing these experiments?
I am doing them.
Look over here, here.
Up here.
My name is Raman.
Actually, I'm a Bianca's nephew.
And like him, I'm also an expert in science.
Three nabbehown.
Huh?
And this is my robot called Dumbo.
Dumbo?
Why Dumbo?
Because he's an expert in goofing up.
In every job he does.
Three nabbehown.
Stop it!
Hey!
Huh?
Three nabbehown.
But why is he throwing out everything?
Because I have given him the order to clean up the house.
Three nabbehown.
Hmm.
Only call your config, Sima.
Three nabbehown.
Huh?
Not a boy.
Three nabbehown.
Stop it, you bitch!
Oh!
How do I stop your Dumbo?
By pressing off his switch.
Huh?
Three nabbehown.
I am.
Oh no!
He is now going to iron up all the clothes.
Hmm?
So what's the big problem in that?
Well the problem is Dumbo will also iron those clothes which everyone is already wearing.
Oh!
I am all the clothes.
Who is this?
Who?
I am.
Stop it!
Leave me!
Who?
I am the God!
Who is this?
injured.
I am.
Oh?
All the clothes.
I am.
I am all flourish.
All the clothes.
I am.
Huh?
This is the button to switch him off.
Oh!
94!
Looks like Boss is going to touch hard weight this time.
Yes, just like him.
Hey Boss, just three more to go.
And you will touch 100.
Oh!
Huh?
Do you think I am a nom school?
No, of course not Boss.
Though I don't know about the nom bit,
but you are definitely not just a school.
You both are going to have it from me.
Stop!
Stop both of you!
Huh?
Come on Kaliya, let them be.
Why don't you do your work and let me and my boys do whatever we want to, huh?
That reminds me, Bhim.
Professor Dhumke had called you to his laboratory for some work.
It's about something called a lawa card.
Everyone just calls Bhim all the time.
He doesn't Professor Dhumke to ever call me for any work.
Had that been of any use, he would have surely called.
What did you just say?
I was just saying that he or the one and only
were famous wrestler of Dholakpur.
So you can walk in un-invited anywhere Kaliya boss.
You got a point.
So let's go.
This is my lawa card.
But where is the lawa uncle?
Well kids, if I had really put boiling lawa into this,
do you think making this machine, I mean this car would have been possible?
Of course not.
Hot molten lawa can even melt steel.
And when it cools down, it becomes solid and heavy as a rock.
That is why instead of using actual lawa in this car of mine,
I have used certain new chemicals which mimic the properties of real molten lawa.
But what does this car actually do uncle?
Well actually I have made this for car racing you see.
For car racing I was thinking if you can trial this car out, Bhim.
Why Bhim? Why not me?
Yeah, what were you doing behind the bushes?
He was hardly listening to what you were discussing.
If anyone gets to trial this car first, that should be me.
He would be able to understand the intricacies of this car or not.
Instead of understanding intricacies, boss understands delicacies better.
Although all the controls are inside the car, but for the sake of convenience,
I have made this remote for it.
Which would be used by us?
Down, dole, dole.
No bro.
Dole, dole, stop it now.
Come on, why can't we both have a little fun Bhim?
I am just driving out everything in this new car.
Kalyo.
Crazy smoke.
Oh no, what's this?
Oh no.
Oh no, the way.
Bhim, pick this.
Don't worry, everything is fine.
Bhim, hope you didn't get hurt and how's Kalyo?
Yes, we are fine, but your car.
Well, let me take this vehicle back to my laboratory.
Oh my bones are aching so badly.
Do you really have any bones?
I thought it's only fat in there.
Oh no.
Greetings, my lord.
Come Bhim, well kids, there's a lovely mountain at the border of Tolakpur called Neely Pahari.
I want you all to go there on a holiday trip.
Whatever trekking gear, tents and all you would need for that,
I'll provide them, consider it a small gift from me.
I'm sure you're all going to enjoy this camping trip.
So are you all willing?
Yes, my lord.
Neely Pahari.
This is nowhere close to the Kalablu.
And why is this called Blue Mountain on Neely Pahari?
You fools!
That's just a name, a name.
Having luck, do's at night is much more fun, guys.
Heaven knows what's there on top of that mountain where that old battery was bought.
Raju, this is a holiday trip.
We are here to have a look at the mountain.
I'll be on guard duty, all of you go to sleep.
Let's go to sleep then.
Be Ms. Protecting Everyone even here.
Lucky does a dole of poor.
But it's a good thing that we're here to have a look at the mountain.
I'm going to sleep.
We're here to have a look at the mountain.
He does a dole of poor.
Let me do the guarding.
But Kalia.
Neely Pahari's expert is Kalia the wrestler.
I'll do the guard duty. Rest will sleep.
I won't sleep.
Neely Pahari's expert.
Kalia.
I'll do the guard duty.
And he's snoring away.
What happened?
Kalia, we have been robbed.
What?
Someone else is also here.
Come on, guys.
Come on.
Catch the thieves.
Teach us.
You guys and you?
All our campings, staff.
What are you doing at Neely Pahari now?
What is this?
Dole of poor's beam will scale.
Neely Pahari soon.
Ades are all buffoons.
By sending such a message to Pahal Manpur,
you've definitely insulted us, beam.
I'll never stoop so low.
Now you're lying since you're scared, beam.
We've come here for a few days on a trip, Kichak.
My dear citizens of Kerala.
Today is one of the happiest days in all our lives.
This ancient idol, which was stolen from our state,
nearly a thousand of years ago,
has been successfully recovered and brought back to our state
after years of searching.
This unique idol was the pride of our state
and will always remain so.
We will install it back in its temple in the forthcoming festival.
Now no one can snatch it from our state ever again.
Yes, no one except me.
Guards go!
Oh!
My lord, whatever happened is indeed very sad,
but please don't waste your time worrying about it.
That unknown thief will be caught very shortly.
All our people are waiting eagerly for the festival.
Many more arrangements are yet to be made
and this year the special invitation of the festival
has already been sent to your friend his majesty of Thulakpur King Indravarma.
98, 99, 100.
Are you ready now?
Not as yet.
Ready guys?
Not so fast.
I'm coming now.
Hmm?
Where is everyone hiding?
I could always catch them so easily.
Hmm?
Oh yes, this technique is not going to work.
I have got to use my brain a bit
and use this yummy laddo.
Oh!
I found one last laddo was left in my back friends.
Well, this is the only one I have.
Oh!
Hey, beam you're out.
Anyone would do this for such a nice laddo.
I agree completely.
Now this last laddo is all mine.
My, my, my, my, my.
Well, not so easily Jaggu.
Oh!
Finally this laddo is in the hands of its rightful owner.
In that case, I should be its only rightful owner.
So, huh?
You better admit that today's not your day beam
give up now.
The game is over.
The game is not over yet my friend
because I don't give up that easily.
Huh?
Well, we may have just one laddo
but if you agree we all can share it.
Where kids?
There can be no shortage of laddoos
till your ten to nondis there.
Yeah, you can all have them.
Oh!
What nonsense is this?
Hold, I say.
You can't escape from us.
God's, catch that thief.
Don't let him run away.
Wait, I'll catch this rascal.
This thief is quite a jile.
Hey boss, we never knew you were so good at head banging.
Oh really?
Then let me bang your knuckleheads now.
I must say this boy is so strong.
Huh?
What?
You better have some good explanations ready for this, mister.
Huh?
Hey, he's just a young boy.
I will teach this muddy a nice lesson right now.
Just wait.
Hold on Kaliya.
Let's first find out.
Why this boy attempted to steal this amulet?
I know how to make him speak.
No wait Kaliya.
Let me ask him.
You could have easily escaped.
But I know for sure you're not a robber.
And you're surely in some kind of trouble.
Tell us everything.
Maybe we can be of some help to you.
No, no, don't cry.
No one is your enemy out here.
And believe me, all of us are going to help you.
Take a look.
I've come all the way here in search of this thing.
This is a picture of the same amulet beam.
Who are you?
And where did you get this from?
My name is Dure.
And my father gave me this map.
When a village was attacked.
Huh?
But who attacked your village?
And what for?
This is not any ordinary amulet.
This is one half of the world's most popular amulet.
This is one half of the most powerful amulet on earth.
Our village has been guarding this amulet for thousands of years.
But a thousand year back,
a crook named Saraku stole this amulet from our village.
He misused the powers of this amulet.
And turned all Africans into his slaves.
But once slave didn't accept this slavery.
His name was Uji.
Uji challenged Saraku's for a fight.
And their battle went on for many days.
Saraku's was much stronger and powerful than Uji.
But Uji didn't give up.
And in his final attack, he broke the amulet into two.
And with a loud bang,
both the halves of the amulet vanished forever.
The secret of finding out and joining the parts of this amulet again
has been written down in this map.
And my father used to protect this map.
To get hold of this secret,
Girboro Atata village.
No.
Who is this Girboro?
He is an evil tribal leader.
And he wants to turn the people of Africa into his slaves once again.
But this is just half the map.
Where is the other half of this?
With my younger brother, Ghanu.
My father told this map into two and gave one half each to both of us.
So where is your brother now?
When Girboro didn't get the map anywhere in the village,
he sent his soldiers chasing us in the jungle.
My brother Ghanu ran away inside the jungle.
Girboro soldiers also followed him into the jungle.
I couldn't be of any help to him.
I got so scared.
Look at this! Back lights!
This means the sun will shine and there will be rain too.
Finally, there will be some rain in Dholakorn.
And then we jump off right down in the puddles.
What's going on?
Aha, beam.
Children come come.
Kalia and Hulu-Hulu are already here to see my kitchen robot.
Kitchen robot?
Yes.
Made of glass, my helper in the kitchen can do so many jobs.
Oh!
Daddy even screamed like Kaya.
Oh no, it's this. The robot is out of control.
Hey, don't move.
Why are you making it?
Chase me or not?
You will just try to make an omelet for your boss.
This way I'll become an omelet myself.
Help me! Help me!
Help me!
No, no, no. We had only pressed a few buttons.
Thank goodness! You did not press all the buttons.
Is the remote not working properly, Professor?
Do you know?
No, beam. This will not stop now.
But we have to stop it.
And Kalia will be in danger.
Help me! Help me!
Help me!
I am sorry, Professor.
I only wanted to stop the robot from hurting Kalia.
Not breaking.
I know, beam.
It's good that this glass is of a different kind.
And I can fix it.